Guide to the Willard Dickerman Straight papers, 1825-1925.
Straight, Willard Dickerman papers, 1825-1925.
- Visual Materials
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Suzuki, Japan 1880-1897 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Childood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Maury, James 1880-1897 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Adult Portraits of Willard Straight
    - New York, Plattsburg 1914-1918 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Adult Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Portraits 1914-1918 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Adult Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. 1914-1918 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Adult Portraits of Willard Straight
    - U.S. Army 1914-1918 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Adult Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Underwood & Underwood 1914-1918 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Adult Portraits of Willard Straight
    - World War I 1914-1918 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Baldwin Coolidge, Boston Massachusetts 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Dress 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - J.E. Smith's Studios, Bordentown, New Jersey 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Japan 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - New Jersey, Bordentown 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Oliver, Oswego, New York 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Portraits 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Transportation, Jinrikshas 1880-1901 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Brands Studios, Chicago, Illinois 1881-1887 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Canova Studios, Chicago, Illinois 1881-1887 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Fassett, Chicago, Illinois 1881-1887 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Oliver, Oswego, New York 1881-1887 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Portraits 1881-1887 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. 1881-1887 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Childhood Portraits of Hazel Straight
    - Brands Studios, Chicago, Illinois 1882-1887 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Childhood Portraits of Hazel Straight
    - Lovell, Oswego, New York 1882-1887 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Childhood Portraits of Hazel Straight
    - Portraits 1882-1887 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Childhood Portraits of Hazel Straight
    - Straight, Hazel H. 1882-1887 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Childhood Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Baldwin Coolidge, Boston Massachusetts 1182-1887 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Childhook Portraits of Hazel Straight
    - Canova Studios, Chicago, Illinois 1882-1887 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Beardsley, Oswego, New York 1875-1880 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Canova Studios, Chicago, Illinois 1875-1880 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Portraits 1875-1880 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Rocher, Chicago, Illinois 1875-1880 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Emma Dickerman Straight
    - Straight, Emma D. 1875-1880 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Tombs of Henry and Emma Straight (annotated)
    - California, Pasadena n.d. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Tombs of Henry and Emma Straight (annotated)
    - Straight, Emma D. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Tombs of Henry and Emma Straight (annotated)
    - Straight, Henry H. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Tombs of Henry and Emma Straight (annotated)
    - Tombs n.d. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Bend, Beatrice 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Cameras 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Dress 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - France, Chamonix 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Social Life 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Sports 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends (annotated)
    - Tennis 1907-1910 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Friends
    - Croly, Herbert D. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Friends
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners n.d. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Friends
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Friends
    - Straight, Dorothy W. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Friends
    - Straight, Willard D. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Willard and Dorothy Straight
    - China, Peking 1909-1912 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Willard and Dorothy Straight
    - France, Divonne 1909-1912 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Willard and Dorothy Straight
    - Portraits 1909-1912 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Willard and Dorothy Straight
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1909-1912 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Willard and Dorothy Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. 1909-1912 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Willard Straight and Dorothy Straight
    - Ceylon 1909-1920 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - En Route to England
    - Abriatic (SHIP) 1914 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - En Route to England
    - Davison, Henry P. 1914 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - En Route to England
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1914 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - En Route to England
    - Ships 1914 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - En Route to England
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1914 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - En Route to England
    - Straight, Willard D. 1914 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Dress 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Egan, Martin 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - New York, Westbury 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Rhode Island, Narragansett 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Seascapes 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Social Life 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Straight, Willard D. 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Narragansett and Westbury
    - Tennis 1913-1916 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - World War I (annotated)
    - American Expeditionary Forces 1915-1918 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - World War I (annotated)
    - Architecture, Interior 1915-1918 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - World War I (annotated)
    - France, Langres 1915-1918 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - World War I (annotated)
    - People, Groups of Westerners 1915-1918 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - World War I (annotated)
    - People, Unidentified Individuals 1915-1918 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Displays of Artwork by Willard Straight
    - Arden Gallery, New York, New York 1921 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Straight Children
    - Children 1913-1925 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Straight Children
    - New York, Westbury 1913-1925 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Straight Children
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1913-1925 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Straight Children
    - Straight, Michael W. 1913-1925 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Straight Children
    - Straight, Whitney W. 1913-1925 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Straight Children
    - Straight, Willard D. 1913-1925 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Straight Family
    - Children 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Straight Family
    - Elmhirst, Lecnard K. 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Straight Family
    - Massachusetts, Woods Hole 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Straight Family
    - New York, Westbury 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Straight Family
    - People, Identified Groups of Westerners 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Straight Family
    - Straight, Michael W. 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Westbury and Woods Hole
    - Children 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Westbury and Woods Hole
    - Massachusetts, Woods Hole 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Westbury and Woods Hole
    - New York, Westbury 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Westbury and Woods Hole
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Westbury and Woods Hole
    - Straight, Michael W. 1921-1924 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Michael Whitney Straight
    - Children 1921-1925 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Michael Whitney Straight
    - Massachusetts, Woods Hole 1921-1925 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Michael Whitney Straight
    - New York, New York 1921-1925 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Michael Whitney Straight
    - New York, Westbury 1921-1925 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Michael Whitney Straight
    - Portraits 1921-1925 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Michael Whitney Straight
    - Straight, Michael W. 1921-1925 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Westbury
    - New York, Westbury 1922, 1925 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Westbury
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1922, 1925 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Westbury
    - Children 1922-1925 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Westbury
    - Portraits 1922-1925 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Woods Hole
    - Children 1923-1924 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Woods Hole
    - Massachusetts, Woods Hole 1923-1924 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Woods Hole
    - Portraits 1923-1924 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Beatrice Whitney Straight, Woods Hole
    - Straight Beatrice W. 1923-1924 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Michael Whitney Straight
    - Children 1924 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Michael Whitney Straight, Woods Hole
    - Massachusetts, Woods Hole 1924 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Michael Whitney Straight, Woods Hole
    - Portraits 1924 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Michael Whitney Straight, Woods Hole
    - Straight, Michael W. 1924 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Westbury
    - Architecture, Exterior 1925 c. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Westbury
    - Gardens 1925c. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Westbury
    - New York, Westbury 1925c. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Westbury
    - Straight, Whitney W. 1925c. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Westbury
    - Transportation, Airplanes 1925c. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Westbury
    - Transportation, Automobiles 1925c. (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Raquette Lake
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Raquette Lake
    - Landscapes n.d. (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Raquette Lake
    - New York, Raquette Lake n.d. (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Pictures of Europe
    - Architecture, Exterior n.d. (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Pictures of Europe
    - Europe n.d. (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Pictures of Europe
    - France n.d. (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Great-grandmother Beard (genealogical annotation)
    - Beard, N.C. (Mrs.) n.d. (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Great-Grandmother Beard (genealogical annotation)
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Bordentown Military Institute
    - Bordentown Military Institute 1896-1897 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Bordentown Military Institute
    - New Jersey, Bordentown 1896-1897 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Bordentown Military Institute
    - Portraits 1896-1897 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Bordentown Military Institute
    - Straight, Willard D. 1896-1897 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Portrait of Friends and Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - C.E. Lemunyon, Peking and Tientsin, China 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Davison, Henry P. 1910 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Portraits 1910 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Boissonnas & Caponier, Paris, France 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Calhoun, William J. 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Harriman, Florence J. 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Histed, London, England 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Marvin, George D. 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Portraits of Friends and Associated (autographed, annotated)
    - Strauss Payton 1910c. (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Phillips, William 1913 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Portraits 1913 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Bend, Beatrice 1913 c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1913c (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Harris & Ewing, Washington, D.C. 1913c (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Logan, James A. 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Marvin, George D. 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - McCoy, Frank 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Miles, Basil 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Seventeen-Eighteen (1718) H Str. 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Straight, Willard D. 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Seventeen-Eighteen H Street
    - Washington, D.C. 1913c. (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Histed, London, England 1913-1917 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Langfier Ltd., London, England 1913-1917 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - New York, Plattsburg 1913-1917 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Portraits 1913-1917 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. 1913-1917 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Underwood & Underwood 1913-1917 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Baby Pictures
    - Portraits 1915 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Baby Pictures
    - Misses Selby, New York, New York 1915c. (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Baby Pictures
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1915c. (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Baby Pictures
    - Straight, Whitney W. 1915c. (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Baby Pictures
    - Straight, Willard D. 1915c. (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Bend, Beatrice 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Casenave, Maurice 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Clark, George 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Clark, Gertrude 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Clark, Herman 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Fletcher, Henry P. 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Harriman, Florence J. 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Kinnicutt, May 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Lovell, Oswego, New York 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - New York, Oswego 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - New York, Westbury 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Newkirk, Laura R. 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Phillips, William 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Portraits 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Social Life 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Straight, Willard D. 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Underwood & Underwood 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Friends and Relatives
    - Weddings 1911-1917 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Photographs and Paintings
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - Davis, Cecil n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - Goldbeck, Waiter D. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - Louis Mcquaid, Westbury, New York n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - Murphy, Grayson P. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - P.A. Juley, New York, New York n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - Paintings n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - Straight, Dorothy W. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Photographs of Paintings
    - Straight, Willard D. n.d. (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Dorothy Straight in Sedan Chair
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1911c. (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Dorothy Straight in Sedan Chair
    - Transportation, Sedan Chairs 1911c. (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Camp of Instruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York
    - World War I 1915 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Camp of Instruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York (annotated)
    - Camp of Intruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York 1915 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Camp of Instruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York (annotated)
    - New York, Plattsburg 1915 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Camp of Instruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York (annotated)
    - Preparedness Movement 1915 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Camp of Instruction, Regular Troops, Plattsburg, New York (annotated)
    - U.S. Army 1915 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - English Country Parties
    - Dress 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Parties
    - England 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Parties
    - French, Charles 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Parties
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Parties
    - Phillips, William 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Parties
    - Social Life 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Parties
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Parties
    - Straight, Willard D. 1912 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - English Country Houses
    - Architecture, Exterior 1912 c. (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - English Country Houses
    - Gardens 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - English Country Parties
    - England 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - English Country Parties
    - People, Unidentified Groups of Westerners 1912 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - English Country Parties
    - People, Unidentified Individual Westerners 1912 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - English Country Parties
    - Dress 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - English Country Parties
    - England 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - English Country Parties
    - Gardens 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - English Country Parties
    - Straight, Dorothy W. 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - English Country Parties
    - Straight, Willard D. 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - English Country Parties
    - Women 1912c. (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - A.H. Smith, Salem, Massachusetts n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - E.L. Fowler, Chicago, Illinois n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Lee, Mary n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Morley, Margaret W. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Nesbitt, Oswego, New York n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - New York, Oswego n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Straight, Hazel H. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Straight, Henry H. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight
    - Williams, Anna L.B. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Henry and Emma Straight (annotated)
    - Straight, Emma D. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Willard Straight's Family, Later Prints
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Willard Straight's Family, Later Prints
    - Straight, Emma D. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Willard Straight's Family, Later Prints
    - Straight, Henry H. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Hazel Henrietta Straight Sanborn
    - Nesbitt, Oswego, New York 1890-1912 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hazel Henrietta Straight Sanborn
    - Northrop, Oswego, New York 1890-1912 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hazel Henrietta Straight Sanborn
    - Portraits 1890-1912 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hazel Henrietta Straight Sanborn
    - Shayes, Oswego, New York 1890-1912 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hazel Henrietta Straight Sanborn
    - Straight, Hazel H. 1890-1912 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hazel Henrietta Straight Sanborn
    - Straight, Willard D. 1890-1912 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hazel Henrietta Straight Sanborn
    - Wolven Studio, Poughkeepsi, New York 1890-1912 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Hazel S. Sanborn and Family
    - Lovell, Oswego, New York n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hazel S. Sanborn and Family
    - Margaret D.M. Brown n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hazel S. Sanborn and Family
    - Portraits n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hazel S. Sanborn and Family
    - Sanborn, Dorothy n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hazel S. Sanborn and Family
    - Sanborn, Joan n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hazel S. Sanborn and Family
    - Sanborn, Robert S. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Hazel S. Sanborn and Family
    - Straight, Hazel H. n.d. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Straight Family Portraits
    - Portraits 1910 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Straight Family Portraits
    - Rembrant, Chicago, Illinois 1910 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Straight Family Portraits
    - Seigel Studio, Chicago, Illinois 1910c. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Straight Family Portraits
    - Straight, Dorothy Louise 1910c. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Straight Family Portraits
    - Straight, Ella Mae 1910c. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Straight Family Portraits
    - Straight, Orlando W. (Mrs.) 1910c. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - Cornell U. 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - George Cary, Architect 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - New York, Buffalo 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - New York, Ithaca 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - Portraits 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - Howes Art Gallery, Ithaca, New York 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - Portraits 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - Stephens, Henry M. 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Cornell (annotated)
    - Straight, Willard D. 1897-1901 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Histed, London, England 1900-1915 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Portraits 1900-1915 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Straight, Willard D. 1900-1915 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Underwood & Underwood 1900-1915 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Portraits of Willard Straight
    - Harris & Ewing, Washington, D.C. 1900-1915 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - C.E. Lemunyon, Peking and Tientsin, China 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Associates (autographed, annotated)
    - Casenave, Maurice 1904-1911 (Box 66, Folder 9)